iosnoops.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy | iOSnoops

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by _TechSnoops LLC_ (“we”). We operate several websites, including _iOSnoops.com_. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

Your privacy is critically important to us. Our goal is to be transparent about what information we collect, and how we use it. We have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our websites. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our websites.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. We only disclose logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors of our websites choose to interact with us in ways that require our websites to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who leave comments on _iOSnoops.com_ to provide a name and email address. We collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with our properties. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our websites. For instance, we may monitor the most popular pages and/or comments on _iOSnoops.com_. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property or rights, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of our websites and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users (in this specific case, personally-identifying information will not be published). We take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our websites, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features of our websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If some or all of _TechSnoops LLC_ ‘s assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that  _TechSnoops LLC_ goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that would potentially be transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of some or all _TechSnoops LLC_ ‘s assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Advertisement

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.

### Comments

Comments left by users on our websites are the sole responsibility of the person posting them. You agree not to post comments that are off topic, defamatory, obscene, abusive, threatening, considered “spam”, or an invasion of privacy. Violators may be banned.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

_Last update: May 5, 2017. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us via our[contact page](httpd://www.iosnoops.com/contact-us/).  
_

This policy was inspired by Automattic.  
It is released under a [Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/).
